<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="how_we_design" name="CIDS How We Design">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
        <link rel="stylesheet" href="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/scss/how_we_design.scss"/>
<!--        <script type="text/javascript" src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/js/cidsjquery.js"/>-->
<!--        <script type="text/javascript" src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/js/gallery.js"/>-->
<!--        <script type="text/javascript" src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/js/owl.js"/>-->
<!--        <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.2/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css"/>-->
<!--        <link rel="stylesheet" href="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/scss/owl.carousel.min.css"/>-->
<!--        <link rel="stylesheet" href="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/scss/owl.theme.default.min.css"/>-->
<!--        <link rel="stylesheet" href="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/scss/animate.css" />-->
<!--        <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css"/>-->
        <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0" />

    <section class="commercial-banner">
        <div class="comm-banner">
            <!-- <p class="headP">How we Design</p> -->
            <h1>Impactful Designs</h1>
            <h1><span>Inspired By The Future.</span></h1>
            <div class="pText">
                <!-- <p>At CIDS.DESIGN We perceive 'design' as a soulful bridge connecting human experiences and memories. We
                    strongly believe that everything starts and ends with a great design. Therefore, we craft
                    future-focused spaces that inspire and captivate.</p> -->
                    <p>We strongly believe that everything starts and ends with a great design. Therefore, we draft future-focused spaces that inspire and captivate.</p>
            </div>
            <div class="hbtns">
                <a class="explore" href="/contactus">Get In Touch <img class="unionpng"
                        src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/images/Union.png" /></a>

            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="owl-carousel owl-theme commercialBanner">
            <div class="item">
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/what-we-do-banner.png"/>

            </div>
            <div class="item">
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/what-we-do-banner.png"/>

            </div>
            <div class="item">
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/what-we-do-banner.png"/>
            </div>
        </div>


    </section>

    <section class="why-different">
        <div class="why-diff-left">
            <!-- <h2>How we Do </h2> -->
            <h1>Our Process To Delivering A Heart-Winning Design</h1>
            <p>Navigating a successful commercial interior design project necessitates exceptional planning, a
                professional approach, and a concrete understanding of spaces – so they can be functional while being
                aesthetically pleasing. At CIDS.DESIGN, we assist our clients in conceptualising phenomenal interiors
                that not only exude warmth and positivity but also amplify the property value.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="why-diff-right">
            <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/how-do.png" />
        </div>
    </section>

    <section class="process proc2">
        <div class="process-rgt">
            <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/loondfeel.png" />
        </div>
        <div class="process-lft">
            <h1><span class="numbering">01</span>DEFINING THE LOOK &amp; FEEL.</h1>
            <p> We undertake a detailed introductory discussion of every project's requirements, paying undivided
                attention to your vision and aspirations. Fine-tuning into the context of the project's brief and the
                broader design goals in detail, our team sets the tone, look, and feel of each and every space with
                utmost perfection. To define the overall aesthetics of the interiors, we create ideas, form
                inspirational mood boards, and give creative design directions. At CIDS.DESIGN, we also closely look at
                the flow and functionality of spaces within the experimental parameters of the built environment.</p>
        </div>
    </section>

    <section class="process proc1">
        <div class="process-lft">
            <h1><span class="numbering">02</span>CONCEPT DEVELOPMENT.</h1>
            <p> Our professionals create plans for each space while exploring layouts for rooms, lobbies, cafes, and
                others with appropriate lighting, artwork, and furnishing – all articulated to determine how individual
                elements can be used. A series of concept boards are built, forming the basis for materials and
                furniture specifications needed for the interior finishings. At CIDS.DESIGN, we extensively consider the
                interior detailing required for flooring, walls, and structures by taking into account the key focal
                points such as accent decor, fireplaces, artefacts, and more. We also pay great attention to how the
                interiors relate to the outdoor surrounding areas like gardens and landscapes. </p>
        </div>
        <div class="process-rgt">
            <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/concept-dev.png" />
        </div>
    </section>

    <section class="process proc4">
        <div class="process-rgt">
            <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/designndproc.png" />
        </div>
        <div class="process-lft">
            <h1><span class="numbering">03</span>DESIGN &amp; PROCUREMENT.</h1>
            <p>Every project detail is strategically analysed, coordinated, and optimised to drive innovation and
                transformation. We provide comprehensive designs, interior plans, and elevations with technical and
                detailed 3D designs for different spaces. Our sourcing team assembles uniquely blended fabrics,
                furniture, and equipment (FF&amp;E), paying extra attention to materials, textiles, decorative lighting, and
                furnishing. Each interior we create elevate by art and collectibles meticulously sourced from the best
                parts of the world. Incredible emphasis is laid on the quality and standards that enable us to surpass
                client expectations while also being under budget. </p>
        </div>
    </section>

    <section class="process proc3">
        <div class="process-lft">
            <h1><span class="numbering">04</span>COMPLETION &amp; HANDOVER.</h1>
            <p>Drawing upon our industry knowledge and multi-year expertise in offering bespoke interior design
                services, we ensure that all our projects tell different success stories. We work closely with our
                partners and experts during the installation of lighting, furniture, curtains, picture hangings, and
                other equipment. While reaching completion of the program, we dress and style the spaces in accordance
                with our interior design plan for a flawless and smooth handover. The most satisfying part of our work
                is adding the finishing touches and final details, making the entire project personalised, immaculate,
                and characterful.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="process-rgt">
            <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/completion.png" />
        </div>
    </section>

    <section class="our-services">
        <div class="service-text">
            <!-- <h3>our Services<img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/line.png" /></h3> -->
            <h1>EXCEPTIONAL INTERIOR DESIGNING SERVICES FROM <span>START TO FINISH.</span></h1>
            <p>We provide High-quality interior finishes with no compromise over Quality. We create Innovative &amp; unique
                designs priority on client satisfaction Trusted &amp; budget-friendly</p>
        </div>
        <div class="service-imgs">
            <div>
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/hotels.jpg" />
                <div class="abs-service ">
                    <div class="head-Text">
                        <p>Hotels and</p>
                        <p>Resorts</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="imgPText">
                        <p>Having a deep understanding of the unbreakable connection between hospitality, design, and
                            human experiences, we are committed to unlocking new opportunities and implementing
                            ultra-modern interior design trends that keep your guests returning for more. </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div>
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/resort.jpg" />
                <div class="abs-service ">
                    <div class="head-Text">
                        <p>Bars and</p>
                        <p>Cafe</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="imgPText">
                        <p>Give a fresh perspective to your bar, cafe, or restaurant interior design with us—driving
                            inspiration from the latest and urban styles, CIDS.DESIGN works with the top industry
                            talents to transform any place into an attractive social hotspot.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div>
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/offices.jpg" />
                <div class="abs-service ">
                    <div class="head-Text">
                        <p>Office</p>
                        <p>interiors</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="imgPText">
                        <p>Co-working spaces and offices can greatly benefit from cohesive interior designs that promote
                            energy, zestfulness, and productivity. They aren't just places of work but a hub of
                            communications where new friendships and ideas bloom at CIDS.DESIGN.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div>
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/commercial.jpg" />
                <div class="abs-service ">
                    <div class="head-Text">
                        <p>Commercial </p>
                        <p>Buildings</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="imgPText">
                        <p>Extraordinary ideas emerge from decoding the needs of the people and the community we serve.
                            We deliver high-value and creative commercial interior design solutions that connect people
                            and communities together.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div>
                <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/hospitals.jpg" />
                <div class="abs-service ">
                    <div class="head-Text">
                        <p>Hospitals and </p>
                        <p>Research Centers </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="imgPText">
                        <p>Extraordinary ideas emerge from decoding the needs of the people and the community we serve.
                            We deliver high-value and creative commercial interior design solutions that connect people
                            and communities together.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </section>

    <div class="separartor">
        <img src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/how_design/lline.png" />
    </div>

    <section class="design-journey">
        <div class="journy-inner">
            <h1>Looking To Begin Your Interior Design Journey</h1>
            <h1><span>Want To Consult With an Expert Before You Start ?</span></h1>

            <div class="hbtns">
                <a class="explore" href="/contactus">Contact Us
                    <!-- <img class="unionpng" src="/cids_theme_odoo_15/static/src/img/images/UnionYellow.png" /> -->
                    </a>

            </div>
        </div>
    </section>

        </t>

    </template>
</odoo>