<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="cids_process" name="CIDS Process">
        <section class="cid-process ">
        <div class="process-header">
            <h1>How We Translate Your Vision Into A Successful Project?</h1>
            <p>We connect people and communities together through impactful and creative hospitality
            interior design solutions. The key to our success is to ensure that the end result is a crystal-clear
            reflection of our client’s demands, visions, and aspirations. To transform your ideas into reality,
            we start with a detailed discussion, analyze your project requirements, and offer
            purposeful hospitality interior design services with a striking impact.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="process-types">
          <div>
            <div>
           <img src="https://dev.cids.design/web/image/1934-f0c83f1d/cidConcept.png"/>
           <h2>1.Conceptualization</h2>
           <p>Keeping our client’s goals, budget, timeline, and demands at the forefront, we kick-start the project
           by understanding the scope of work, formulating results-driven design strategies,
           and creating realistic 3D renderings to conceptualize the core vision.</p>
            </div>
          </div>

          <div>
            <div>
           <img src="https://dev.cids.design/web/image/1936-7902ac2b/cideDesign.png"/>
           <h2>2.Design</h2>
           <p>We implement the latest design concepts into our hospitality interior designing approach,
           helping brands to future-proof the success of their properties. At CIDS.DESIGN, we offer a personal touch to
           every project with holistic interior design solutions connected to your brand’s DNA. </p>
            </div>
          </div>

          <div>
            <div>
           <img src="https://dev.cids.design/web/image/1938-073dbb19/cidDelivery.png"/>
           <h2>3.Delivery</h2>
           <p>Our multidisciplinary team manages the entire design process to ensure all projects meet creative,
           technical, and operational requirements. Extensive care is taken throughout the design journey to make every
           single detail reflect
           the initial conceptualization without any shortcuts.</p>
            </div>
          </div>
        </div>
    </section>
    </template>
</odoo>